﻿1. Visual Studio :	Microsoft Visual Studio is an integrated development environment (IDE) from Microsoft. 
			It is used to develop console and graphical user interface applications along with Windows 
			Forms or WPF applications, web sites, web applications, web services, and also Windows Store
			apps in both native code together with managed code for all platforms supported by Microsoft Windows,
			Windows Mobile, Windows CE, .NET Framework, .NET Compact Framework and Microsoft Silverlight.

2. Eclipse :		Eclipse is an integrated development environment (IDE). It contains a base workspace and an extensible 
			plug-in system for customizing the environment. Written mostly in Java, Eclipse can be used to develop 
			applications. By means of various plug-ins, Eclipse may also be used to develop applications in other 
			programming languages: Ada, C, C++, COBOL, Fortran, Haskell, JavaScript, Lasso, Perl, PHP, Python, R, 
			Ruby (including Ruby on Rails framework), Scala, Clojure, Groovy, Scheme, and Erlang. It can also be 
			used to develop packages for the software Mathematica. Development environments include the Eclipse 
			Java development tools (JDT) for Java and Scala, Eclipse CDT for C/C++ and Eclipse PDT for PHP, among others.

3. NetBeans :		NetBeans is an integrated development environment (IDE) for developing primarily with Java, but also with
			other languages, in particular PHP, C/C++, and HTML5.[2] It is also an application platform framework for 
			Java desktop applications and others.

4. Android Studio :     Android Studio is an integrated development environment (IDE) for the Android platform.

5. Xcode :		Xcode is an integrated development environment (IDE) containing a suite of software 
			development tools developed by Apple for developing software for OS X and iOS.